<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Herbavist</string>
    <string name="jahe">Ginger (Zingiber officinale) Ginger is a rhizome plant that contains various kinds of nutrients, such as fiber, minerals, vitamins, and so on. Because of these contents, ginger is believed to have various benefits for body health. Function: Ginger is often used as a spice in cooking and drinks. Apart from that, ginger also has anti-inflammatory and antioxidant properties which can help relieve nausea, reduce joint pain, and support healthy digestion.</string>
    <string name="lidah_buaya">Aloe Vera (Aloe vera) Aloe vera is a green plant that has no bones and has thick flesh, also called gel. This part offers a multitude of benefits because of the active substances it contains. This plant is often used as a basic ingredient for beauty products because it contains: Folic acid. Function: Aloe vera has good skin healing and hydrating properties. Aloe vera gel is often used to soothe burns, skin irritation, and as an ingredient in skin and hair care products.</string>
    <string name="sambiloto">Sambiloto (Andrographis paniculata) Sambiloto is a type of wild plant that has many benefits, namely being able to treat various diseases. Function: Sambiloto is known to have antimicrobial, anti-inflammatory and immunomodulatory properties. This plant is often used in traditional medicine to treat various health problems, such as fever, flu, coughs and respiratory tract infections.</string>
    <string name="kunyit">Turmeric (Curcuma longa) Turmeric is a medicinal plant in the form of a shrub and is an annual (perennial) that is spread throughout the tropical regions. Turmeric plants grow abundantly and wildly around forests/former gardens. It is thought to originate from Binar at an altitude of 1300-1600 m above sea level, some also say that turmeric comes from India. Function: Turmeric contains an active compound called curcumin, which has anti-inflammatory and antioxidant properties. Turmeric is often used in traditional medicine to help reduce inflammation, improve the immune system, and support digestive health.</string>
    <string name="daun_kemangi">Basil Leaves (Ocimum basilicum) Basil is an annual plant that grows upright with many branches. This plant is a shrub that can reach 100 cm in height. The flowers are arranged in upright clusters. The leaves are long, erect, spur-shaped or oval, light green in color and smell good. The tip of the leaf can be blunt or sharp, reaching 5 cm in length. The surface is serrated or flat. It smells like cloves and tastes bitter. Function: Basil leaves contain compounds such as eugenol, linalool, and estragol which have antimicrobial and anti-inflammatory properties. Basil leaves are often used in cooking as a flavoring and are also consumed to help relieve inflammation, improve the immune system, and reduce stress.</string>
    <string name="tentang_aplikasi">This application contains information about herbal plants that are often used by Indonesian people</string>
    <string name="kembali">Back</string>
</resources>